<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ad Manager</string>
    <string name="ad_id_title">AdId:</string>
    <string name="ad_id_value"><tt>adId: </tt></string>
    <string name="ad_id_tracking_limited_value"><tt>isLimitedAdTrackingEnabled: </tt></string>
    <string name="ad_id_limited_true">You aren\'t traceable via your AdId</string>
    <string name="ad_id_limited_false">You are traceable via your AdId</string>
    <string name="ad_id_description"><tt>AdId</tt> is a unique per device, per user, user resettable device identifier represented as a 128 bit string. Permitted usages are Advertisement Personalization, due to the nature of this particular API, google plans to phase it out. However, google\'s timeline for phasing it out is not certain, what is certain is google introduced the Privacy Sandbox in February 2022, introducing APIs like the Topics API and stating they would eventually deprecate the <tt>AdId</tt> APIs, the deprecation date I would suggest is between the mid 2030s or 2040s.</string>
    <string name="app_set_id_title">AppSetID:</string>
    <string name="app_set_id_value"><tt>id: %1$s!</tt></string>
    <string name="app_set_id_scope_dev"><tt>SCOPE_DEVELOPER = 2</tt></string>
    <string name="app_set_id_scope_app"><tt>SCOPE_APP = 1</tt></string>
    <string name="app_set_id_scope_dev_desc">This ID identifies a developer on the app store, and cannot identify individual apps the developer made.</string>
    <string name="app_set_id_scope_app_desc">This ID identifies a single app from a developer, and can identify individual apps the developer made.</string>
    <string name="app_set_id_scope_value">scope = %1$d!</string>
    <string name="app_set_id_unusable"><tt>AppSetIdManager</tt> is unavailable and cannot be used for identification</string>
    <string name="app_set_id_description"><tt>AppSetId</tt> is a unique identifier for usages in analytics, spam detection, frequency capping, and fraud prevention. This ID can be scoped to the application itself, in which case the app will have a unique ID. or scoped to the developer, meaning different apps a developer makes will still have the same ID. When the app is made on the play store with a registered account, most of the time it is developer scoped, but in cases where play services are disabled, or when the app is not from the play store, then the ID can be application scoped.</string>
    <string name="measurement_api_status_disabled"><tt>measurementApiStatus: MEASUREMENT_API_STATUS_DISABLED = 0</tt></string>
    <string name="measurement_api_status_enabled"><tt>measurementApiStatus: MEASUREMENT_API_STATUS_ENABLED = 1</tt></string>
    <string name="measurement_api_status_enabled_desc"><tt>MeasurementManager</tt> attribution APIs are available to apps and the OS can send attribution events to HTTPS servers.</string>
    <string name="measurement_api_status_disabled_desc"><tt>MeasurementManager</tt> attribution APIs cannot be used by apps. The OS will <b>not</b> send attribution events to HTTPS servers.</string>
    <string name="measurement_api_description"><tt>MeasurementManager</tt> is used to allow apps to register advertisement-related events to Attribution URLs in a privacy-preserving way. Attribution is split in 2 different event types: Source events, registered when an ad is shown to the user and/or the user interacts with an advertisement. And Trigger events are registered when a conversion occurs, which includes but is not limited to: app installs, first app open, signup, purchase, etc. The Android OS matches source and trigger events and when a valid attribution is found, a report is scheduled and in the future, sent to an ad-tech endpoint. Reports do not contain user-identifying data but rather contain small integers for identification, app/origin identifiers (package name, URL), etc. Reports are scheduled days to weeks ahead. Aggregated reports are generated server-side from many attribution events submitted by devices, they do not represent individual users.</string>
    <string name="unavailable"><tt>unavailable</tt></string>
</resources>